[
  {
    "user": "649ed5cf0726cd3196875383",
    "question": "649b3db2d50f2c4652f63bc0",
    "response": "working with machines",
    "createdBy": "Camron Giles",
    "lastModifiedBy": "Camron Giles"
  },
  {
    "user": "649ed5cf0726cd3196875383",
    "question": "649b4aa063832f79b117190e",
    "response": "no",
    "createdBy": "Camron Giles",
    "lastModifiedBy": "Camron Giles"
  },
  {
    "user": "649ed5cf0726cd3196875383",
    "question": "649b4aa063832f79b117190f",
    "response": "creative",
    "createdBy": "Camron Giles",
    "lastModifiedBy": "Camron Giles"
  },
  {
    "user": "649ed5cf0726cd3196875383",
    "question": "649b4aa063832f79b1171910",
    "response": "independently",
    "createdBy": "Camron Giles",
    "lastModifiedBy": "Camron Giles"
  },
  {
    "user": "649ed5cf0726cd3196875383",
    "question": "649b4aa063832f79b1171911",
    "response": "yes",
    "createdBy": "Camron Giles",
    "lastModifiedBy": "Camron Giles"
  },
  {
    "user": "649ed5cf0726cd3196875383",
    "question": "649b4aa063832f79b1171912",
    "response": "no",
    "createdBy": "Camron Giles",
    "lastModifiedBy": "Camron Giles"
  },
  {
    "user": "649ed5cf0726cd3196875383",
    "question": "649b4aa063832f79b1171913",
    "response": "yes",
    "createdBy": "Camron Giles",
    "lastModifiedBy": "Camron Giles"
  },
  {
    "user": "649ed5cf0726cd3196875383",
    "question": "649b4aa063832f79b1171914",
    "response": "fast paced",
    "createdBy": "Camron Giles",
    "lastModifiedBy": "Camron Giles"
  },
  {
    "user": "649ed5cf0726cd3196875383",
    "question": "649b4aa063832f79b1171915",
    "response": "no",
    "createdBy": "Camron Giles",
    "lastModifiedBy": "Camron Giles"
  },
  {
    "user": "649ed5cf0726cd3196875383",
    "question": "649b4aa063832f79b1171916",
    "response": "yes",
    "createdBy": "Camron Giles",
    "lastModifiedBy": "Camron Giles"
  },
  {
    "user": "649ed5cf0726cd3196875383",
    "question": "649b4aa063832f79b1171917",
    "response": "no",
    "createdBy": "Camron Giles",
    "lastModifiedBy": "Camron Giles"
  },
  {
    "user": "649ed5cf0726cd3196875383",
    "question": "649b4aa063832f79b1171918",
    "response": "yes",
    "createdBy": "Camron Giles",
    "lastModifiedBy": "Camron Giles"
  },
  {
    "user": "649ed5cf0726cd3196875383",
    "question": "649b4aa063832f79b1171919",
    "response": "no",
    "createdBy": "Camron Giles",
    "lastModifiedBy": "Camron Giles"
  },
  {
    "user": "649ed5cf0726cd3196875383",
    "question": "649b4aa063832f79b117191a",
    "response": "yes",
    "createdBy": "Camron Giles",
    "lastModifiedBy": "Camron Giles"
  },
  {
    "user": "649ed5cf0726cd3196875383",
    "question": "649b4aa063832f79b117191b",
    "response": "no",
    "createdBy": "Camron Giles",
    "lastModifiedBy": "Camron Giles"
  },
  {
    "user": "649ed5cf0726cd3196875383",
    "question": "649b4aa063832f79b117191c",
    "response": "no",
    "createdBy": "Camron Giles",
    "lastModifiedBy": "Camron Giles"
  },
  {
    "user": "649ed5cf0726cd3196875383",
    "question": "649b4aa063832f79b117191d",
    "response": "yes",
    "createdBy": "Camron Giles",
    "lastModifiedBy": "Camron Giles"
  },
  {
    "user": "649ed5cf0726cd3196875383",
    "question": "649b4aa063832f79b117191e",
    "response": "not important",
    "createdBy": "Camron Giles",
    "lastModifiedBy": "Camron Giles"
  },
  {
    "user": "649ed5cf0726cd3196875383",
    "question": "649b4aa063832f79b117191f",
    "response": "hybrid",
    "createdBy": "Camron Giles",
    "lastModifiedBy": "Camron Giles"
  }
]